[
  {
    "question": "This football team won World Cup 2022?",
    "options": {
      "a": "Argentina",
      "b": "France",
      "c": "Croatia"
    },
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "This football team won in Champions League 2021/2022?",
    "options": {
      "a": "Liverpool",
      "b": "PSG",
      "c": "Real Madrid"
    },
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "This runner broken world record in Berlin 2022 year?",
    "options": {
      "a": "Mo Farah",
      "b": "Eliud Kipchoge",
      "c": "Kenenise Bekele"
    },
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who won 'Indian Wells Masters' in 2023 year?",
    "options": {
      "a": "Sabalenka Aryna",
      "b": "Swiatek Iga",
      "c": "Rybakina Elena"
    },
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "He is a spanish professional tennis player who have a record in Grand Slam men's single titles?",
    "options": {
      "a": "Rafael Nadal",
      "b": "Novak Djokovic",
      "c": "Carlos Alcaraz"
    },
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which footballer has scored the most goals in World Cup history?",
    "options": {
      "a": "Pele",
      "b": "Ronaldo",
      "c": "Miroslav Klose"
    },
    "answer": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Usain Bolt's blistering 100m world record time?",
    "options": {
      "a": "9.58 seconds",
      "b": "9.60 seconds",
      "c": "9.56 seconds"
    },
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Chicago Cubs and Boston Red Sox play which sport?",
    "options": {
      "a": "Basketball",
      "b": "Baseball",
      "c": "Soccer"
    },
    "answer": "b"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the Premier League's all-time top scorer?",
    "options": {
      "a": "Alan Shearer",
      "b": "Harry Kane",
      "c": "Wayne Rooney"
    },
    "answer": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which sport do teams compete to win the Stanley Cup?",
    "options": {
      "a": "Baseball",
      "b": "Soccer",
      "c": "Hockey"
    },
    "answer": "c"
  }
]
